I'll tell you something I didn't intend to
tell you in this video.
2021, a lot of my friends got rich,
really rich.
It was only when I went to their houses
that I realized, "Fuck." Whilst I was
playing "Call of Duty"
and having the best years of my life,
other people did so
well that their kids will never have to
work.
In these massive houses, beautiful cars.
And it's not that I'm jealous of their
success, it's that I'm annoyed
that I didn't
use that time right.
And I've got friends now at the moment
being content pussies.
And I say to them,
"Ignore everything you feel today.
Just ask yourself this:
If things get harder,
which very likely they could, will
you be able to forgive yourself for not
going all in now?" Because there's a part
of me that eats away at myself for the
opportunities that I missed four or five
years ago, and I'm making up for it now.
Got a chip on my shoulder, for sure.
But if you do not maximize the next two,
three years, if I don't do it, I'm not
going to be able to forgive myself. Now,
there's so much opportunity.
Cameras that you can put in your car,
wireless mics that make you sound good,
algorithms that show people content,
your content,
when they don't even follow you.
To be a content pussy in 2026
is just one of the worst decisions,
because it
is a decision. You have two paths in life,
action, inaction.
Your life right now
is a series of decisions of things you've
done and things you
haven't.
And even if you never buy my programs,
never join my courses, never join
my mentorship, whatever,
which most of you won't, and that's fine,
if there's one
skill that you really need to develop for
the future, it's to not
be a content pussy. Everything
that I've managed to do in the last few
years,
books, events, cars, houses, fiancée,
child, social media
content opened everything.
And just don't sleep on
that opportunity because I
honestly don't know
if you'll be able to forgive yourself in a
few years' time.
You're scared, I get it. So was everyone.
But some of us just decided to get on with
it anyway. I think George St.
Pierre said, "Courage is not
that you're not scared, it's that you
are scared and
you do it anyway." Links in the
description.